ke.com.pk 2018-05-14

# Privacy Policy - K-Electric

  * >
  * **Privacy Policy**

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site.

This privacy policy sets out how K-Electric Ltd. (Hereinafter referred to as, “KE”, “we” and “us” as the context so requires) uses and protects any information that you give us when you use this Website.

KE is committed to ensure that your privacy is duly protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this Website; you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this Privacy Policy (hereinafter referred to as the, “Policy”).

We may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page occasionally to ensure that you are updated with the latest changes.

We may collect the following information:

  * full name and job title
  * contact information including address, CNIC number, phone numbers, email address, passwords, etc.
  * demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
  * other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping.
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional email about special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * To collect comments or ideas that you may send us.
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes if applicable. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may further use the information to customise the website according to your interests and preferences.

We are committed to ensure that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. We only use personal data fairly and lawfully, and ensure that it is kept secure. Nothing is stored online and our systems are extremely well protected. We will not pass the information that you give us to any organisations beyond KE, our associated and subsidiary companies and our agents and service providers, unless we inform you otherwise and obtain your consent. 

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. 

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be held responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement and therefore we waive any responsibility and liability with respect to the same. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question. 

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please visit our Contact Us page and send us a request as soon as possible. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
